(Sheldon:)Here's a fun Postal fact.
Yeah, the inside of our mailbox
(Sheldon:)is under federal jurisdiction.
(Sheldon:)So, if you broke
my right thumb,
(Sheldon:)that's Pasadena city police.
(Sheldon:)But if you broke
my left thumb,
(Sheldon:)that's the FBI.
(Leonard:)If I'm going to jail, I'm killing him,
not breaking his thumb.
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I got a letter
from my Meemaw.
(Sheldon:)Umm. Smell this.
(Penny:)What is that?
(Sheldon:)Uh, roses, bengay,
and Dr. Schools' foot powder.
Yeah, "Grandma",
by Calvin Klein.
Yeah, the last time I got
a hand written letter,
(Penny:)it was from someone who told me
I parked like a blind person.
(Leonard:)That someone has a name.
(Sheldon:)Uh, thank you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Meemaw got
a new set of teeth.
(Sheldon:)Oh, but then
she found her old ones.
(Sheldon:)Oh, so now the new ones are
just gonna be her church teeth.
(Leonard:)Fun. Like your
Comic-Con Spock ears
(Leonard:)and your around
the house Spock ears.
I park fine!
(Sheldon:)Oh, my goodness,
she's coming to visit!
(Leonard:)Oh, it'll be nice
to finally meet her.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you are going
to love her.
(Sheldon:)She is the kindest, sweetest
woman you'll ever meet.
Yeah, unless you're a gopher
digging up her vegetable garden.
(Sheldon:)In that case, you can expect
(Sheldon:)to have your head bashed in
with a shovel.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪